<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Artiom Kovnatsky: Portfolio &amp; Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Artiom Kovnatsky: Portfolio &amp; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>#0: Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beyond_obvious/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beyond_obvious/intro/</guid>
      <description>Истина, выраженная в форме (например, написанная, сказанная..), перестаёт ей быть, включая и то, что я пишу...исключения, как правило, составляют метафоры, притчи, сказки, пословицы...музыка Прочитав этот тренинг-статью, читатель:
сделает гимнастику для мышления, что позволит, быть может, увеличить осознанность и, соответсвенно, привнести больше свободы в своё мышление и, как следствие, в свою жизнь периодически, думается, тренинг-статью стоит перечитывать, делать пометки, пытаясь понять изложенные смыслы и связи между ними &amp;hellip;также будет иметь представление:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1: Синергия в движении: Люди как динамические системы и Бизнес как поток</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beyond_obvious/dynamic_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beyond_obvious/dynamic_system/</guid>
      <description>Истина, выраженная в форме (например, написанная, сказанная..), перестаёт ей быть, включая и то, что я пишу...исключения, как правило, составляют метафоры, притчи, сказки, пословицы...музыка Прочитав этот тренинг-статью, читатель:
сделает гимнастику для мышления, что позволит, быть может, увеличить осознанность и, соответсвенно, привнести больше свободы в своё мышление и, как следствие, в свою жизнь периодически, думается, тренинг-статью стоит перечитывать, делать пометки, пытаясь понять изложенные смыслы и связи между ними &amp;hellip;также будет иметь представление:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/services/</guid>
      <description>Data Specialist You want to monetize your data and need a way to “activate” it
Details The company had customer interaction data, but it wasn’t clear how to use it. I developed a recommendation algorithm that, based on the limited data left by the customer, allowed us to make an initial assessment of the likelihood of the person becoming a customer. This allowed more efficient use of the limited resources of the sales department, focusing on those most likely to benefit from interaction with the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Φιλοσοφία | Philosophy | Философия</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Leave everything, at the very least, no worse than it was before you. I follow this principle in both big life decisions and everyday matters, from major life choices to something as simple as using a restroom at a conference.
Оставляй всё, как минимум, не хуже, чем было до тебя. Я придерживаюсь этого принципа как в глобальных вопросах, так и в повседневных делах: от важных жизненных решений до посещения туалетной кабинки на конференции.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#0: Metaphorical Autobiography or The Bunker Stories of the Professor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/omega/meta-bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/omega/meta-bio/</guid>
      <description>Fig. 1 The Metaphorical Professor&#39;s Dwelling Truth, expressed in form (e.g., written, spoken...), ceases to be truth, including what I am writing... exceptions are usually metaphors, parables, tales, proverbs... music. After reading this, the reader will have an understanding of:
who they are dealing with where I came from what my values are where I am going if we are on the same path and for how long, if yes Ω.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1: The Boat, Kandinsky 7.0, and ChatGPT 42.0 or Value-Meaning Journeys</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/omega/lodka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/omega/lodka/</guid>
      <description>Truth, when expressed in form (for example, written, spoken..), ceases to be such, including what I am writing... exceptions usually include metaphors, parables, fairy tales, proverbs... music By reading this training-article, the reader:
will do mental gymnastics, which may increase awareness and, consequently, bring more freedom into their thinking and, as a result, into their life periodically, it seems, the training-article is worth rereading, making notes, trying to understand the meanings expressed and the connections between them &amp;hellip;will also have an understanding:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#7: The Image of the Future or Andrey&#39;s Journey with Baba Yaga&#39;s Magic Ball of Thread</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/omega/opa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/omega/opa/</guid>
      <description>Fig. 0 Imagine your image of the future. Ω symbolizes the end/final point; Ω is Omega, the last letter of the Greek alphabet. Questions: what &amp;ldquo;colors&amp;rdquo; can be used to paint the future why &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;isms&amp;rdquo; are not a solution why hypotheses, and not &amp;ldquo;I know&amp;rdquo; From the author Earlier, the main question was raised: why and how do we interact with each other? Here, I will &amp;ldquo;paint&amp;rdquo; a possible image of the future with &amp;ldquo;colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
